<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Login Registration Jetpack Compose</string>
    <string name="heythere">Hey There,</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create An Account</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="fullname">Fullname</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_heading">Terms And Condition</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">UPI D.I. Serayu. By accessing or using our services, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions (\"Terms and Conditions\").\n\nDefinitions\nUser: Any individual or entity that accesses or uses our services, and is thereby considered a user of the service.\nService: All services provided by the Company, including but not limited to the website, mobile applications, and other services.\nContent: Any information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages, or other materials.\nAcceptance of Terms\nBy accessing or using our services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with any part of these terms, then you may not access the services.\n\nUse of Services\nUser Accounts: You may be required to create an account to access certain features of our services. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your account.\nUser Conduct: You agree not to use the services for any unlawful purpose or in violation of any applicable laws or regulations. You also agree not to:\na. Violate the rights of others.\nb. Upload or transmit viruses or other harmful components.\nc. Engage in any form of automated use of the services.\nIntellectual Property: The content provided through the services is the property of the Company or its licensors and is protected by intellectual property laws. You may not reproduce, modify, distribute, or otherwise use any of the content without the Company\'s written permission.\nTermination\nWe reserve the right to terminate or suspend access to our services immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever.\n\nLimitation of Liability\nIn no event shall the Company, its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages.\n\nGoverning Law\nThese Terms and Conditions shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of [Jurisdiction], without regard to its conflict of law provisions.\n\nChanges to Terms\nThe Company reserves the right to modify or replace these Terms and Conditions at any time. It is your responsibility to check the Terms and Conditions periodically for changes.\n\nContact Us\nIf you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, please contact us at [Contact Email].\n\nBy using our services, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
</resources>
